{
  "kind": "dropdown",
  "title": "EPgrade1WBDropdown.csv",
  "questions": [
    {
      "title": "Choose the correct question",
      "activity": [
        {
          "question": "___",
          "options": [
            "What your name?",
            "What's your name?"
          ],
          "correct": "What's your name?",
          "type": "text"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Choose that or those.",
      "activity": [
        {
          "question": "What are ___ ?",
          "options": [
            "that",
            "those"
          ],
          "correct": "those",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "What's ___ ?",
          "options": [
            "that",
            "those"
          ],
          "correct": "that",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "What's ___ ?",
          "options": [
            "that",
            "those"
          ],
          "correct": "that",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "What are ___  ?",
          "options": [
            "that",
            "those"
          ],
          "correct": "those",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "What's ___ ?",
          "options": [
            "that",
            "those"
          ],
          "correct": "that",
          "type": "text"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Choose the correct word.",
      "activity": [
        {
          "question": "___ is a zebra.",
          "options": [
            "This",
            "That"
          ],
          "correct": "This",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "___ are lions.",
          "options": [
            "These",
            "Those"
          ],
          "correct": "These",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "___ are zebras.",
          "options": [
            "These ",
            "Those"
          ],
          "correct": "Those",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "___ is a zebra.",
          "options": [
            "This",
            "That"
          ],
          "correct": "That",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "___ a gorilla",
          "options": [
            "This",
            "That"
          ],
          "correct": "That",
          "type": "text"
        },
        {
          "question": "___ an elephant.",
          "options": [
            "This",
            "That's"
          ],
          "correct": "That's",
          "type": "text"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}